[
  {
    "question": "With Amazon Virtual Private Cloud (Amazon VPC), what is the smallest size subnet you can have in a VPC?",
    "options": [
      "/30",
      "/26",
      "/28",
      "/24"
    ],
    "correctIndex": 2
  },
  {
    "question": "With Amazon Virtual Private Cloud (Amazon VPC), what is the maximum size IP address range you can have in a VPC?",
    "options": [
      "/30",
      "/28",
      "/16",
      "/24"
    ],
    "correctIndex": 2
  },
  {
    "question": "You need to allow resources in a private subnet to access the internet. Which of the following must be present to enable this access?",
    "options": [
      "NAT gateway",
      "Security groups",
      "Route tables",
      "Network access control lists"
    ],
    "correctIndex": 0
  },
  {
    "question": "Which AWS networking service enables a company to create a virtual network within AWS?",
    "options": [
      "AWS Direct Connect",
      "AWS Config",
      "Amazon Route 53",
      "Amazon Virtual Private Cloud (Amazon VPC)"
    ],
    "correctIndex": 3
  },
  {
    "question": "True or False? Private subnets have direct access to the internet.",
    "options": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "correctIndex": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "Which component of AWS Global Infrastructure does Amazon CloudFront use to ensure low-latency delivery?",
    "options": [
      "AWS edge locations",
      "AWS Availability Zones",
      "AWS Regions",
      "Amazon Virtual Private Cloud (Amazon VPC)"
    ],
    "correctIndex": 0
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following is an optional security control that can be applied at the subnet layer of a VPC?",
    "options": [
      "Network ACL",
      "Firewall",
      "Security group",
      "Web application firewall"
    ],
    "correctIndex": 0
  },
  {
    "question": "What happens when you use Amazon Virtual Private Cloud (Amazon VPC) to create a new VPC?",
    "options": [
      "Three subnets are created by default in one Availability Zone.",
      "An internet gateway is created by default.",
      "Three subnets are created by default: one for each Availability Zone.",
      "A main route table is created by default."
    ],
    "correctIndex": 3
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following can be used to protect Amazon Elastic Compute Cloud (Amazon EC2) instances hosted in AWS?",
    "options": [
      "Security group",
      "All of the above",
      "AMI",
      "Internet Gateway"
    ],
    "correctIndex": 0
  },
  {
    "question": "You are a solutions architect... When you create a VPC, you assign it to an IPv4 Classless Inter-Domain Routing (CIDR) block of 10.0.1.0/24... How many IP addresses are available?",
    "options": [
      "251",
      "246",
      "256",
      "250"
    ],
    "correctIndex": 0
  },
  {
    "question": "Your private subnets need to connect to the Internet while still remaining private. Which AWS-managed VPC component allows you to do this?",
    "options": [
      "Security Groups",
      "Internet Gateway",
      "NAT Gateway",
      "Network ACL"
    ],
    "correctIndex": 2
  },
  {
    "question": "Which type of firewall has both ALLOW and DENY rules and operates at the subnet level?",
    "options": [
      "Network Access Control List (NACL)",
      "Web Application Firewall (WAF)",
      "Security Groups",
      "Network Address Translation (NAT)"
    ],
    "correctIndex": 0
  },
  {
    "question": "You need a logically isolated section of AWS, where you can launch AWS resources in a private network that you create. What should you use?",
    "options": [
      "Availability Zone (AZ)",
      "A VPC",
      "A NAT instance",
      "Network ACL"
    ],
    "correctIndex": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "Your VPC needs to connect with the Internet. Which VPC component can help?",
    "options": [
      "NAT Gateway",
      "Security Group",
      "Internet Gateway",
      "Network ACL"
    ],
    "correctIndex": 2
  },
  {
    "question": "A VPC is available in which scope:",
    "options": [
      "Regional",
      "Global",
      "Availability Zone"
    ],
    "correctIndex": 0
  },
  {
    "question": "A public subnet is accessible from the Internet while a private subnet is not accessible from the Internet.",
    "options": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "correctIndex": 0
  },
  {
    "question": "A public subnet is an Availability Zone resource.",
    "options": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "correctIndex": 0
  },
  {
    "question": "The largest IPv4 CIDR block size in a VPC is /20.",
    "options": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "correctIndex": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "Each subnet must be associated with a route table.",
    "options": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "correctIndex": 0
  },
  {
    "question": "NACL (Network ACL) is a firewall which controls traffic from and to an EC2 instance.",
    "options": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "correctIndex": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "True or false? Unlimited services are available with the AWS Free Tier to new AWS customers for 12 months following their AWS sign-up date.",
    "options": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "correctIndex": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "Testing recovery procedures, and automatically recover from failure are design principles of Performance Efficiency.",
    "options": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "correctIndex": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "True or False? AWS Key Management Service (AWS KMS) enables you to assess, audit, and evaluate the configurations of your AWS resources.",
    "options": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "correctIndex": 1
  }
]